All right so now we're familiar with the basics of media player in Android.
现在我们已经熟悉 Android 中的 MediaPlayer 的基础知识
We need to take what we learned with the music player app and
我们需要将在 MusicPlayer 应用中学到的知识
apply it to our Miwok App.
运用到我们的 Miwok 应用中
But, first, we need to figure out where we should put the media player code
但首先 我们需要知道应该将 MediaPlayer 代码
within our Miwok App.
放在 Miwok 应用的什么地方
Now in the app demo, I showed you that when we click on a list item,
在应用演示中 我展示了当我们点击某个列表项时
we should play the audio pronunciation for the selected word.
我们应该为所选单词播放音频发音
So, how do we do this programatically in the Java code?
我们该如何通过 Java 代码实现呢？
Well, one way to do it is to add a click listener on to each list item.
一种方法是在每个列表项上添加一个 clickListener
So, remember from lesson one, we defined a click listener for
在第 1 节课中 我们为每个类别视图定义了 clickListener
each category view and then we implemented the OnClickListener for
然后为 Numbers 类别 Family 类别
the numbers category, the family category and all the other categories.
和其他所有类别实施了 OnClickListener
With that logic,
明白这一点后
we could create a different OnClickListener for each list item.
我们可以为每个列表项创建一个不同的 OnClickListener
But if we were to have, say, a thousand words in our list,
但是 假设列表中有一千个单词
that would be a lot of OnClickListener objects.
那么就会有太多的 OnClickListener 对象
Well, of course, the android team thought that this would be a common
当然 Android 团队已经想到处理列表视图中的
request, handling clicks on list items in the list view.
列表项上的点击操作是个常见请求
So they came up with the way for us as developers to easily add this behavior.
所以他们想出了一种方法 让开发者能够轻松地添加这一行为
To help us figure out how to do this, let's go through this exercise.
为了帮助大家理解如何实现这一操作 我们来看一个练习
I'd like you to research how we can define what should happen
请研究下我们可以如何定义当列表项被点击时
when a list item gets clicked on and, more specifically, what method should we
应该发生的情况 更具体地说
call on the ListView, as well as what are the inputs to that method?
我们应该对 ListView 调用什么方法 以及该方法的输入值是什么？
And I'd like you to specify the data type for each input.
请指定每个输入值的数据类型
Go ahead and write your answers here.
请将答案写在这里
Note that they'll be no code changes required in this exercise.
注意 在此练习中 你不需要更改任何代码
You'll be modifying the app in the next exercise.
你将在下个练习中修改应用